(Sun Honglei)
(Li Naiwen)
(Guo Jingfei)
(Liu Yuning)
(Gong Jun)
(Chen Xingxu)
(Wang Yuwen)
(Lin Yi)
=Wow The World S2 Extra Episode=
We're going to play a game about unity
and teamwork.
Let me go over
the rules for everyone.
(Game Rules)
There are eighteen cars in front of you.
Ten cushions are hidden
among these cars.
Each cushion is printed with one letter.
These letters can spell out
the French word "bonjour",
which means "hello".
Within eight minutes, you need to
find these cushions
and, in the designated area over there,
spell out "bonjour".
The eight of you will
be split into two teams.
Each team of four will
be tied together with a rope.
The production team has set up
multiple cameras around the cars.
These cameras will take photos
every ten seconds.
If any member of your team
gets caught on camera,
one warning will be issued.
If any team accumulates five warnings,
you'll lose this round outright
and have to restart the challenge.
When the cameras are shooting,
you need to get inside a car to hide,
so you won't be caught on camera.
Important note.
Some car doors are locked.
Besides, still photographers
inside certain cars
will take snapshots with their phones.
Getting caught by their phones
will also trigger a warning
and count toward your total.
Does everyone understand?
Understood.
Let's get ready.
I have a question.
For example, within these ten seconds,
we get into the car,
but there's a still photographer inside.
We'll still get caught, right?
Right.
So we just can't get into this car.
So there definitely aren't any letters
inside that car, right?
Not necessarily.
(Already figured out)
Then we just have to
take out the still photographer.
No need.
Just grab their phones.
Director, for the still-photographer's
phone or camera,
can we grab it?
Just thinking about it gets him excited.
Look at Honglei, he's like a pit bull.
The moment he thinks about
being able to grab it.
Once he bites down, he's not letting go.
Come on.
Now, split into teams of four.
Then we'll set off from opposite sides.
So, what now?
Split teams, then make the plan.
(Too tall to be an advantage)
Taller people are harder to hide, right?
I think we should
assign people based on body size, right?
I think
we should put one girl on that team.
Then
(Tall Trio)
you guys are at a disadvantage.
Let's just call our team
the Disadvantage Team.
Yuning, come here.
Then...
You or Chaoyue...
The two of us.
If the two of us are on the same team...
- Actually...
- Invincible.
Right.
Because...
What do you mean?
We're the big brains.
- We two are the big brains.
- This is a physically demanding game,
Fei.
- Really?
- It also requires mental smarts.
Okay, you stay on this team.
This is a game all about cooperation.
Stay calm.
Calm.
Don't panic.
Don't panic
and move in sync.
First of all,
when you hear ten, nine, eight, seven,
six, five, four, three, two, one,
at that moment,
you must get inside a car and hide.
Find the nearest one.
Okay, you go over there.
You four are one team.
(That's settled)
There are four of us, okay.
Two girls on our team?
Okay.
They're smaller,
so there are plenty of spots...
No.
So we need to give them one girl.
They're all tall.
Then you come here.
See.
You're treating me...
Come when called, leave when waved.
Both teams, make sure
you communicate a lot.
Because the letters you find
might be duplicates.
Is Xingxu good at this?
I'm good.
(Don't worry, I'm here)
You can trust me, bro.
Then let's follow Xingxu's lead.
We need one person
to give unified commands.
No problem.
Don't get messy.
Can we tie this rope anywhere?
Anywhere.
(Strategizing)
We need to find a safe car.
The safe car
will be our starting point.
Let's come up with a plan.
First, figure out
how we can finish this task quickly.
Here's the thing.
We need to set up
a safe house in advance.
So when the next shot comes,
we can rush back right away.
(First-opened cars)
So open these two front cars first.
I think
we'll definitely start from
inside a car.
Right?
Outside.
We start from outside the car.
So first, find a safe car.
Get in first.
That's the most important thing.
The two team leaders
think pretty much alike.
Here's the thing.
Since we're starting from two sides,
(Two teams start from opposite sides)
let's just open all the doors.
So we can see the other side
at a glance.
See the other side at a glance.
- Open all doors.
- Okay? Let's open them all.
- Right.
- Let's go this way, okay?
Okay.
We'll deal with unexpected situations
only if they come up.
- Okay.
Okay.
Come on.
- There are bound to be surprises.
- Let's go.
It's over.
Victory is ours.
Come on, the Bonjour team.
Come on.
- Bonjour.
- Bonjour team.
"Stupid Pig" team.
[*Bonjour and Stupid Pig sound alike]
Bonjour team.
Come on.
Okay, let's go.
Three, two, one.
Bonjour team.
- Let's go.
- Victory is ours.
Okay.
Victory is ours, let's go!
Totally out of sync,
all jumbled.
Let's go.
- Come on.
- I'll go first.
No rush, don't panic.
Right, don't panic.
Right.
Ready.
Three.
Two.
One.
(Challenge begins)
Start.
(Countdown)
Ten.
Nine.
Get in the car.
B.
(Got the letter "b")
Go.
Let's go back.
(Opened the next car door in advance)
Get in.
Six.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
Take the photo.
No rush.
No.
Let's go.
Wait.
Eight.
You go first.
- No, wait.
- Seven.
Why?
No.
His timing is off.
Ten.
Nine.
Don't rush.
Eight.
Seven.
Six.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Almost.
Take the photo.
Let's go.
Get ready to head back.
Eight.
Okay, we still have time.
- We still have time.
- Six.
Get in the car.
Get in.
I'm in.
Any letters?
No.
Then I'll open the ones over there.
In a second.
After this round,
we'll open the ones over there.
After unlocking, head right back.
(Target car)
Go diagonally.
Right.
Go.
Get down after the photo signal.
Five.
(Snapshot ready)
Four.
- Three.
- Go.
Quick, get in.
(First warning triggered)
Take the photo.
That scared me.
Okay.
Take a breather.
Wait.
(Choosing to observe for one round)
Wait, take a look.
Let's listen first.
Come on.
Eight.
Wait for this round to end.
Go.
Naiwen, go.
Eight.
Seven.
Six.
Five.
Four.
Three.
(Time is tight, open one more door)
No need, don't get in.
No need.
Take the photo.
(Second warning triggered)
(Don't get it, just follow orders)
What do you mean?
We're out of time, so we won't run.
Three.
Two.
(Third warning triggered)
You're really...
(Nai is outside the car again)
Obviously.
It caught me.
Take a breather.
Go.
Then open...
Open the diagonal car door and run back.
This way.
This is our fallback route.
Five.
Here.
(Emergency evacuation)
Back.
Three.
Two.
Take the photo.
(Warning triggered once)
This route is a bit long.
We could have gone in just now.
No, because there is a time limit.
Which way? What's the route?
Go with what you said earlier.
Three.
- Should we go this round?
- Two. Take the photo.
Go.
Deng Kai, go.
Slow down, don't rush.
Let's go. We have time.
Get in.
- Quick.
We have time.
No rush.
Two.
(Successfully got in the car)
Take the photo.
Okay.
One more.
That one's too far away.
Which car are we heading for?
This car.
Got it.
(Target car)
The diagonal one, right?
Diagonal.
Six.
Then I'll open the right-side door.
No.
No, you need to stay with us.
Take the photo.
Go.
- Go.
- Ten.
Quick.
(Don't forget to open the next car door)
Go.
Four.
Three.
Get in.
Two.
- Okay.
- Take the photo.
I opened that one over there.
You guys...
Big man in black.
Step aside, please.
Let me use it.
Shift your body a bit.
Thanks.
(Got the letter "o")
O.
Two.
We need two letters Os.
Ten.
Nine.
I'll open that car door.
Wait.
Seven.
Open that one.
- Six.
- Open doors of the two back cars.
Have you checked the car at the back?
Not yet.
Then let's go check those two cars.
- Those two are electric doors.
- Take the photo.
They can't be opened.
No.
(Leaving first)
- Go.
Slow down.
Slow down, Naiwen.
I know.
Seven.
Open it.
Six.
- It's locked.
- Five, four.
Three.
Two.
Take the photo.
(Fourth warning triggered)
Where's the cushion?
(Empty again)
Nothing at all?
Which way?
That way.
Go diagonally.
I opened this one.
I just opened it.
(Foresight)
Just opened it.
Four.
Wait.
Three.
Two.
Take the photo.
Go.
Hold it well.
Ten.
Nine.
Eight.
Got one.
Get in, quick.
Six, five, four, three.
- Got it?
- Two.
Got one letter "r".
(Got the letter "r")
Only "r".
Okay.
Ten, nine, eight, seven,
six, five, four,
three, two.
Take the photo.
Go.
Ten, nine, eight, seven, six,
(Opened the car door in advance again)
five,
four,
three,
two.
I opened the one over there again.
What's this?
This is...
It's a "j".
(Are you sure?)
This is "r".
R.
Are you sure?
No, it's "j".
This is "r".
Don't we need "r"?
- We don't need "r".
- We have it.
Seven.
Okay.
No rush.
It's dangerous now.
Four.
I'll go outside first.
I'll go outside.
Two.
Take the photo.
Go.
(Countdown)
Slow down.
Game over.
(Other team unaware game over)
I'll open this one.
We can throw it out.
No.
Which car should we open next?
Don't rush.
Right side.
No, just throw it on the ground.
Otherwise, they'll pick it up again,
thinking we need it.
No, they won't.
They won't come here.
Game over.
We lost?
The game is over.
Come on, Deng Kai.
We found four cushions.
No cushions on our side.
That's normal.
They're throwing challenges at you
on purpose.
Actually, by the time
all four of us got out of the car,
the count had already reached five.
Here is the situation.
This is where the difficulty lies.
While we were opening the car doors
on this side,
Deng Kai tried
opening the car door on the other side.
We can open them at the same time.
Time is sufficient.
Right.
Then...
But we have to
follow one person's lead
and get into a safe car.
That way we can move faster
and stay steady.
Yes, that's right.
But all electric on my side.
The only manual one was locked.
If they were all electric...
If most of your doors are electric,
you'll just have to run back.
- Don't get in any car hastily.
- Right, he's correct.
Just now, Li Naiwen pushed me hard,
and Yuwen was getting into the car,
so I had to knee her
and give her a shove.
That was purely instinct.
The countdown has already hit one,
of course, I was getting anxious.
(Summarizing)
Let's stay steadier this round, okay?
It's fine.
Even if we lose, we must not get caught.
He is such a good actor
because he fully believes in
the given circumstances.
- Do you think...
- Yes.
If you don't get in, they'll shoot you.
Yes.
Come on, let's cheer up.
Go for it.
Let's say four words.
Quiet, peaceful, healthy, positive.
Okay?
One, two, three.
Quiet.
Peaceful.
Healthy.
Positive.
Let me tell you
what the coolest play is.
We sacrifice two rounds of time
- to open all the doors.
- No.
(Makes some sense)
- A bit reckless, but not bad. - So cool.
This time,
we start from the middle,
not that side.
Let's just sacrifice one chance
to open all doors.
It's actually really cool.
Just one, two, three, four.
We might just be filmed twice.
Let's just get all the doors open,
then get in one by one.
Okay, let's give it one try.
Right.
Only 20 seconds total.
(Second challenge about to start)
Come on, let's start right here.
Okay.
Like this.
You open the doors on that side,
and I'll open the ones on this side.
Let's start from the last one.
Okay, no problem.
(Switching the search route)
Start from the end.
Let's go.
No rush.
No rush. Let's go.
Go.
(Countdown)
Next one.
Go.
(Open the car doors one by one)
Eight.
Next one.
Six.
Nice.
Five.
Four.
Can't open it?
Three.
Strike a pose.
Take the photo.
(Warning triggered once)
Okay.
Go.
One more.
One more, next one.
Go, quick.
Open the door.
See if it's safe.
(Safe)
Get in.
Five, four, three, two. Take the photo.
Nice.
Look for it.
Check it out.
(No cushion)
Let's go.
No rush.
Take a breather.
Let me turn around.
Okay, adjust the rope.
Let's get in that car first.
Right.
The first one.
That one in front.
No, let's go diagonally.
Wait.
Go this way.
Then head to that one.
Head to that one.
Three, two. Take the photo.
Go.
No rush.
Okay, let's go.
Yuning.
Eight.
Seven.
Got one.
(Cushion +1)
Okay.
Back seats.
(Leaving no corner unchecked)
Nothing.
We're heading over there. Wait a bit.
Wait, right side.
Let's take a break.
Take a break.
Stay composed.
Four, three.
Stay close.
Two.
- Wait, don't rush.
- Take the photo.
Go.
Slow down.
Go, quick.
Go back.
(Can't pull)
Quick.
(Snatches the phone)
Go back.
Quick.
- Throw it.
- Go back.
I snatched it.
He snatched it.
You've got quick hands.
Here, hold one in your arms.
Hold one.
Take the photo.
Over there, let's go.
Go.
He has another camera.
Why are you still getting in?
No.
I didn't check if there's a cushion.
Yeah.
(Seems like none is here)
Then, the diagonal one.
- Go over there?
- Why isn't that door open?
Left side.
Get out from the left side.
Ten.
Nine.
Eight.
Slow down.
Seven.
Six.
Five.
(Got the letter "o")
I found a ring.
(Unexpected gain)
Whose is it?
Yang Chaoyue's, probably.
Okay.
Go to the front one.
Left front.
Take the photo.
Let's go.
I think you left too early.
(Charge)
Nine.
Eight.
(Long legs, stuck in place)
Wait.
Six.
We have time.
Four.
Three.
Two.
Take the photo.
(Got in the car safely)
Where's the cushion?
Nothing behind?
(Completely empty)
Ready.
Three.
Two.
Take the photo.
Ten.
Nine.
Can't get it open.
(Changing the target car)
Seven.
Get in.
- Got one here.
- Six.
Five.
There's one at the back.
Four.
Nothing.
Kai.
Kai, climb up.
(Got it effortlessly)
Go.
Slow down.
Yuning.
Quick.
Six.
Five.
Let's go now.
Go.
Diagonal.
Get down.
(Warning triggered twice)
Two.
(Warning triggered once)
Take the photo.
Go back.
There are ten seconds.
No.
We might not make it in time.
It might be a "bomb car".
You know?
Take the photo. Let's go.
Shall we go?
Wait a moment.
Wait for one more round.
We don't have enough time right now.
The diagonal one.
Diagonal.
Four.
Three.
Two.
Take the photo.
Go.
Eight.
Seven.
Six.
Five.
- Four.
- Open it.
Three.
Two.
Quick.
Take the photo.
(Warning triggered twice)
There is a cushion.
Let's check the cushion.
Got it.
I just threw it over.
Threw it over.
Get ready to head for that car.
Someone's there.
I saw it already.
Grab the camera if he's holding one.
He can't take photos
until it's time for shooting.
(Makes sense)
Come on. Get ready.
Take the photo.
Let's go.
(Still-photographer's phone standby)
Grab the camera if he's holding one.
Seven.
Nice.
Two. Take the photo.
Let's go to the car at the back left.
(Observing cautiously)
Three.
(Countdown)
Two.
Left rear.
- Game over.
- Wait.
Hold on.
Game over.
Let's go.
Come on.
New round, let's do it this way.
Our previous strategy
worked really well.
Open all the doors of two rows first.
Then search each car one by one.
Right, search each car.
Then we have to start from the middle
and open all the car doors.
Right.
Let's start from the middle.
Including the countdown
for the first photo,
we have a total of 25 seconds.
From here all the way to the end,
get into the very last car.
Right, one more thing.
Come out once every ten seconds.
Okay.
Manage your own time.
Another important point.
When you are in the middle,
open the doors of the opposite side too.
That way we can see each other.
We'll know
what letters everyone has picked up.
So where are we starting from?
Still right here?
From the start.
Then you guys take those two rows,
and we'll handle these two rows, okay?
Okay.
Bonjour team.
Let's nail it in one go, okay?
Come on.
Ready, go.
Bonjour team.
Let's nail it in one go.
Okay.
(Third challenge begins)
(Countdown)
Go.
Open it.
Ten.
- Open it.
- Nine.
Go.
- Go.
- Seven.
- Six.
Five.
Go. Split up.
Go.
(Proceeding in sync)
Two.
Go.
Strike a pose.
(Each side triggers one warning)
Let's go.
- Ten.
- This one's manual.
Nine.
Last one.
Seven, six, five,
four, three, two. Take the photo.
(Pushing the limits)
Success.
Good.
Any cushions here?
Yes.
(Got the letter "j")
Wait. Here it is.
Hold on, let me listen.
I need to hear the sound.
Four, three, two. Take the photo.
Go.
Here.
Get in.
Get in, quick.
No rush.
Any letters?
No.
(Checking thoroughly)
Any cushions?
No.
What did you get?
I got a "j".
Over there.
(Found a new cushion
in the car opposite)
There is one over there.
Hold on.
Four, three, two. Take the photo.
Let's go.
Go.
This is...
N.
(Got the letter "j")
J.
J and n.
Come on, follow me.
Get in that car.
Just get in that car.
(Got a cushion)
Get in.
Five, four, three.
There's a photographer.
Grab his phone.
Take the photo.
That one.
Okay.
Come on, let's sit properly first.
Let's go.
Adjust.
No. Let's get seated properly
and make a few adjustments.
Okay.
(Better safe than sorry)
Let's get in
that car.
- Okay.
- Get in that car first.
No one is in that car, right?
Right.
Okay.
Take it first.
Three, two. Take the photo.
Let's go.
Go.
Stay composed.
Eight, seven.
- Go. We have time.
- Six.
Five.
- Four.
- Careful.
Three.
(Got a cushion)
Take a look. Is there anything?
Yes.
Great.
No rush.
No rush, take it easy.
I know.
Tell them to open the door.
(Two teams meet up)
Open the door.
Open the door over there.
Right.
Okay.
I've got a "u".
And "r".
(Syncing the information)
"J" and "n".
I have "u" and "r".
(Sync succeeded)
Get ready.
This car.
That door isn't open.
The diagonal one.
No, this one. This car.
This car.
- There's nothing in that car.
- Don't rush.
Wait.
This car.
This car, Deng Kai.
Got it.
Got it, the one ahead.
Four, three, two. Take the photo.
Go.
Ten, nine, eight, seven,
(Still-shot phone appeared)
six, five, four, three, two.
Take the photo.
(Warning triggered twice)
No.
Let's go.
Can't stay here.
No, you...
Let's go, Deng Kai.
Five, four, three, two.
Take the photo.
(Three warnings triggered)
(Hello)
Wait.
(Third warning triggered)
Let's go.
Ten, nine, eight.
(Got the letter "r")
Over there, bro.
Bro.
Four, three, two.
- Quick.
- Take the photo.
(Got in the car safely)
Any cushions here?
No more.
Wait a bit more.
No rush.
Three.
This one.
Two. Take the photo.
Go.
Ten, nine, eight.
Seven.
Six.
Five.
Four.
(Got the letter "o")
Get in.
O.
Deng Kai, throw this out first.
Throw it out first.
Throw this out.
Five, four.
Wait.
Throw it away now. Pull hands back.
Take the photo.
Go.
That car.
Ten, nine.
What is this?
(Stack up piles of cushions)
Go in and sit inside first.
Four, three, two.
Check underneath to see
if there's anything.
Maybe...
No rush.
We have plenty of time.
There shouldn't be any cushions
on our side.
Nothing.
(Two rows have fully searched)
Call out to them.
Tell them we've finished
searching our side.
Call out
and let them know.
Nothing left our side.
Can they hear you?
(Watch me)
We've finished searching our side.
Done searching.
(Got it)
Watch your head.
Hold on.
Next, let's search the one
on the front left.
Right.
Okay.
Get ready.
Three, two. Take the photo.
Go.
Ten.
Nine.
Eight.
Seven.
Six.
Five.
- Four.
- There's one over there.
(Lock onto the next target)
Three, two.
- Take the photo.
- Quick.
(Got a cushion)
Get in.
Get in, quick!
There's one over there.
Where?
Over here.
Four, three.
Grab that one.
Two. Take the photo.
Let's go.
Go.
Ten.
Nine.
Eight.
Seven.
Six.
(Got a cushion)
Five.
Four.
Three.
That's the only car left
for us to check.
Take the photo.
Let's cross-check.
We've got four already.
R.
J.
We've got four letters.
Jour.
We also have four.
We have "jour".
(Got the letters "j, o, u, r")
Xingxu.
Do you have an "o"?
Yes.
- Do you have a "u"?
- Okay.
Do they have a "u"?
We have "u".
Do they have an "n"?
Do you have an "n"?
Do we have an "n"?
No "n".
N.
We don't have "n".
Don't have "n"?
Is the "u" actually an "n"?
Do you have a "u"?
Aren't these "u" and "n"?
One more time.
(Only "o" missing)
Get in that car first.
Get in that one first.
Okay.
Come on.
Seven.
Six.
Five.
Four.
Three.
- Let's go. Head this way.
- Two.
Take the photo.
Let's go.
Ten, nine, eight.
Quick.
Six, five, four, three.
Two.
(Looking for the last letter)
Take the photo.
Why isn't the right door open?
It's locked.
Nine.
Eight.
Seven.
Six.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
Take the photo.
Let's go.
Ten.
Nine.
Eight.
Seven.
Six.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
Take the photo.
(Found something)
(Successfully got the final letter "o")
Okay.
We can start spelling now.
Let's go.
Go.
This is the safe car.
Safe car.
Bon.
N.
This is "n".
- Jour.
- Jou.
U.
O.
(Spelling complete)
Your final time is
7 minutes and 21 seconds.
Congratulations, everyone!
Challenge succeeded.
♪Turns out that meeting you♪
♪Is the joy hidden in the world♪
♪We still have to experience together♪
♪Exploring the novelty of the world♪
♪This is our wonderful encounter♪
♪I find good scenery
for you along the way♪
♪You are the joy hidden in the world♪
♪I'm lucky to have met you♪
♪That day, we left on a hard road♪
♪In countless late nights,
we exchanged courage♪
♪Our fates have already intertwined♪
♪In each other's life trajectories♪
♪We leave behind
bonds like no other for a lifetime♪
♪Turns out that meeting you♪
♪Is the joy hidden in the world♪
♪We still have to experience together♪
♪Exploring the novelty of the world♪
♪This is our wonderful encounter♪
♪I find good scenery
for you along the way♪
♪You are the joy hidden in the world♪
♪I'm lucky to have met you♪
♪Traveling around the earth♪
♪Tasting all the freshness♪
♪Having traveled all corners♪
♪We still stand shoulder to shoulder♪
♪I'm glad to have met you♪
♪We hum melodiously♪
♪Always trying to write with you♪
♪Thankfully we still share the same sky♪